Guide to the Time Inc. Time-Life News Service Records 1935-1987 MS 3009-RG 14
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Chief of Correspondent Files, 1935-1987; 60.5 Linear feet in 60 record cartons, 1 flat box
  - Subseries I.D. General Files, 1944-1987; 46.95 Linear feet in 46 record cartons, 1 flat box
    - ITT, 1972 (Offsite-box 3159, Folder 2)
    - Iwama, Frank, 1959-1973 (Offsite-box 3159, Folder 3)
    - Iwama, Frank [RESTRICTED], 1975-1981 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Jackson, C.D.: Trips, 1962 (Offsite-box 3159, Folder 4)
    - Jackson, Ed: Dinner, 1986 (Offsite-box 3159, Folder 5)
    - Jackson, R. Edward, 1959-1986 (Offsite-box 3159, Folder 6-8)
    - Jackson, R, Edward [RESTRICTED], 1979-1986 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Jackson, Scoop: Report, 1974 (Offsite-box 3159, Folder 9)
    - Jamieson, 1974-1975 (Offsite-box 3159, Folder 10)
    - Japanese Socialist Party: Coffee Meeting, 1979 (Offsite-box 3159, Folder 11)
    - Jerome, James F., 1973 (Offsite-box 3159, Folder 12)
    - Jerusalem, 1973-1976 (Offsite-box 3159, Folder 13)
    - Jerusalem Audit, 1986 (Offsite-box 3159, Folder 14)
    - Jerusalem Libel Suit, 1975 (Offsite-box 3159, Folder 15)
    - Johannesburg, 1976-1978 (Offsite-box 3159, Folder 16)
    - Johnson, Lyndon, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 3159, Folder 17)
    - Johnson Case, 1956-1960 (Offsite-box 3159, Folder 18-20)
    - Judson, Horace, 1965-1973 (Offsite-box 3159, Folder 21-22)
    - Junkets: Memoranda, 1958-1965 (Offsite-box 3159, Folder 23)
    - K: Miscellaneous, 1971 (Offsite-box 3159, Folder 24)
    - Kalb, Barry, 1970-1986 (Offsite-box 3159, Folder 25-26)
    - Kalb, Barry [RESTRICTED], 1980-1982 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Keane, Thomas: Lunch, 1985 (Offsite-box 3159, Folder 27)
    - Kennedy Administration and Family, 1961-1964 (Offsite-box 3159, Folder 28-29)
    - Khalid, Sunni [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Khoman, Thanat: Washington: 1965 May 10 (Offsite-box 3159, Folder 30-31)
    - Khrushchev, Nikita, 1962-1964, 1971-1976 (Offsite-box 3159, Folder 32-33)
    - Khrushchev, Nikita, 1973-1976 (Offsite-box 3160, Folder 1-2)
    - Khrushchev, Nikita: Strobe and Jerry's Speeches: 1974 April (Offsite-box 3160, Folder 3)
    - Khrushchev Remembers Vol. II, 1974 (Offsite-box 3160, Folder 4)
    - Kingman, Dong, 1977 (Offsite-box 3160, Folder 5)
    - Kissinger, Henry, 1974-1979 (Offsite-box 3160, Folder 6)
    - Klein, Don, 1973-1979 (Offsite-box 3160, Folder 7)
    - Klein, Don [RESTRICTED], 1975-1977 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Koornhof, Pieter, 1979 (Offsite-box 3160, Folder 8)
    - Korn, Jerry, 1980 (Offsite-box 3160, Folder 9)
    - Knox, Marion [RESTRICTED], 1974-1978 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Kraar, Louis, 1963-1972 (Offsite-box 3160, Folder 10-13)
    - Krause, Jean, 1974 (Offsite-box 3160, Folder 14)
    - L: Miscellaneous, 1971 (Offsite-box 3160, Folder 15)
    - Latin America, 1944-1949 (Offsite-box 3160, Folder 16)
    - Latin American Conference, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3160, Folder 17)
    - Law Suits, 1960-1977 (Offsite-box 3160, Folder 18-20)
    - Laxalt, Paul: Lunch, 1979 (Offsite-box 3160, Folder 21)
    - Le Minh, 1970 (Offsite-box 3160, Folder 22)
    - Leadership, 1974 (Offsite-box 3160, Folder 23)
    - Leadership Conference, 1976 (Offsite-box 3160, Folder 24-25)
    - Lee, Young, 1974 (Offsite-box 3160, Folder 26)
    - Leiken, Robert, 1986 (Offsite-box 3160, Folder 27)
    - Letter to Correspondents, 1945-1949 (Offsite-box 3160, Folder 28)
    - Life, 1945-1959, 1969-1972, 1978 (Offsite-box 3160, Folder 29-32)
    - Life [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Life: Clippings and Memoranda, 1972 (Offsite-box 3161, Folder 1-2)
    - Life: Memoranda, 19757-1965 (Offsite-box 3161, Folder 3)
    - Life: Special Reports, 1977 (Offsite-box 3161, Folder 4)
    - Life: Year End, 1974 (Offsite-box 3161, Folder 5)
    - Little Brown, 1972-1976 (Offsite-box 3161, Folder 6-7)
    - Living Conditions: Abroad, 1960-1962 (Offsite-box 3161, Folder 8)
    - Living Conditions: Around World, 1960 (Offsite-box 3161, Folder 9)
    - Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1961-1964 (Offsite-box 3161, Folder 10)
    - London, 1963-1977 (Offsite-box 3161, Folder 11-15)
    - London: Daily Express Contracts, 1960 (Offsite-box 3161, Folder 16)
    - London: Life, 1960-1965 (Offsite-box 3161, Folder 17)
    - London: Party, 19671-1974 (Offsite-box 3161, Folder 18-19)
    - London: Personnel, 1963-1971 (Offsite-box 3161, Folder 20-21)
    - London: Photographer Stringers, 1957-1958, 1966 (Offsite-box 3161, Folder 22)
    - London: Rhodes Scholars, 1965-1969 (Offsite-box 3161, Folder 23-24)
    - London: Rhodes Scholar [RESTRICTED], 1966-1968 (Offsite-box R44)
    - London: Stringers, 1963-1975 (Offsite-box 3161, Folder 25)
    - London: Time, 1964-1967 (Offsite-box 3161, Folder 26)
    - Los Angeles, 1962-1980 (Offsite-box 3161, Folder 27-29)
    - Los Angeles: Personnel, 19762-1972 (Offsite-box 3161, Folder 30)
    - Los Angeles: Personnel [RESTRICTED], 1962-1971 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Los Angeles: Plans, 1975 (Offsite-box 3162, Folder 1)
    - Loughran, Tim, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 3162, Folder 2)
    - Loughran, Tim [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Lowenthal, Abe, 1979 (Offsite-box 3162, Folder 3)
    - Luce, Don: Saigon, etc., undated (Offsite-box 3162, Folder 4)
    - Luce, Henry R., 1957-1965 (Offsite-box 3162, Folder 5-17)
    - Luce, Henry R.: Death, 1967 (Offsite-box 3162, Folder 18)
    - Luce, Henry R.: Trips, 1957-1963 (Offsite-box 3162, Folder 19-21)
    - Luce, Henry R.: Trip: 1964 October 15, 1963-1964 (Offsite-box 3162, Folder 22-24)
    - Lunch Meetings, 1980 (Offsite-box 3162, Folder 25)
    - Luncheons, 1965-1975 (Offsite-box 3162, Folder 26-28)
    - Lunches, 1973-1978 (Offsite-box 3163, Folder 1-3)
    - Luter, John, 1974 (Offsite-box 3163, Folder 4)
    - M: Miscellaneous, 1946-1949, 1959-1975 (Offsite-box 3163, Folder 5-6)
    - M: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1946, 1969 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Melvoin, Jeffrey, 1978-1980 (Offsite-box R44)
    - MacEachen, Allan J.: Speech: 1975 January 23, 1973-1978 (Offsite-box 3163, Folder 7)
    - Madrid, 1964-1978 (Offsite-box 3163, Folder 8-9)
    - Madrid [RESTRICTED], 1964-1972 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Magazine, Minnie, 1970-1980 (Offsite-box 3163, Folder 10)
    - Magazine Development, 1974-1977 (Offsite-box 3163, Folder 11)
    - Maher, Muriel, 1975 (Offsite-box 3163, Folder 12)
    - Mailroom Problems, 1969 (Offsite-box 3163, Folder 13)
    - Man of the Year: Gart, Murray, 1977 (Offsite-box 3163, Folder 14)
    - Marei, Sayed: Coffee: June 23, 1978 (Offsite-box 3163, Folder 15)
    - Marr, Florence, 1969-1974 (Offsite-box 3163, Folder 16)
    - Marr, Florence [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Marshall, Florence, 1972-1975 (Offsite-box 3163, Folder 17)
    - Marshall, Florence [RESTRICTED], 1972-1973 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Marshall, Penny [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Masthead, 1976 (Offsite-box 3163, Folder 18)
    - Martin, Mary [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Martin, Roberta Lee [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Mc: Miscellaneous, 1971 (Offsite-box 3163, Folder 19)
    - McAllister, Jef, 1977 (Offsite-box 3163, Folder 20)
    - McCaslin, Camilla, 1977 (Offsite-box 3163, Folder 21)
    - McColgan, James, 1973-1976 (Offsite-box 3163, Folder 22)
    - McColgan, James [RESTRICTED], 1973-1976 (Offsite-box R44)
    - McCulla, James: Meeting, 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 3163, Folder 23-24)
    - McCulloch, Frank, 1961-1973 (Offsite-box 3163, Folder 25-31)
    - McCulloch, Frank [RESTRICTED], 1963-1972 (Offsite-box R44)
    - McHenry, Donald: Lunch: 1980 May 13 (Offsite-box 3163, Folder 32)
    - McIntyre, James, 1979 (Offsite-box 3163, Folder 33)
    - McLendon, Winzola, 1979 (Offsite-box 3163, Folder 34)
    - McManus, Jason, 1962-1964 (Offsite-box 3163, Folder 35)
    - McNatt, Glenn, 1979-1982 (Offsite-box 3163, Folder 36)
    - McNatt, Glenn [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Offsite-box R44)
    - McWhirter, Bill, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3163, Folder 37)
    - Mecklin, John: Death, 1953-1965, 1971 (Offsite-box 3163, Folder 38-39)
    - Mecklin, John: Death [RESTRICTED], undated (Offsite-box R44)
    - Medical, 1967 (Offsite-box 3164, Folder 1)
    - Melbourne, 1973-1978 (Offsite-box 3164, Folder 2)
    - Melvoin, Jeffrey, 1977-1983 (Offsite-box 3164, Folder 3)
    - Memoranda: Advances: Duplicates, 1974 (Offsite-box 3164, Folder 4)
    - Memoranda: All Staff, 1975-1983 (Offsite-box 3164, Folder 5-11)
    - Memoranda: Miscellaneous, 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 3164, Folder 12)
    - Memoranda: Notes from the Managing Editor, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 3164, Folder 13)
    - Memoranda: Staff, 1974-1979 (Offsite-box 3164, Folder 14)
    - Memoranda: Washington and Worldwide Distribution, 1977 (Offsite-box 3164, Folder 15)
    - Merrick, Frank, 1968-1971 (Offsite-box 3164, Folder 16)
    - Merrick, Frank [RESTRICTED], 1968-1970 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Mexico: 1987 March, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 3164, Folder 17)
    - Mexico: 1987 March [RESTRICTED], undated (Offsite-box R44)
    - Mexico City, 1972-1978 (Offsite-box 3164, Folder 18)
    - Meyers, Burt, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 3164, Folder 19)
    - Meyers, John: China, 1980 (Offsite-box 3164, Folder 20)
    - Miami: 1977 July, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3164, Folder 21)
    - Miami: Party: 1972 Nov. (Offsite-box 3164, Folder 22)
    - Michaels, Marguerite, 1970-1977 (Offsite-box 3164, Folder 23)
    - Michaels, Marguerite [RESTRICTED], 1972-1977 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Middle East, 1973 (Offsite-box 3164, Folder 24)
    - Middle East: Conference, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 3164, Folder 25-26)
    - Middle East: News Tour, 1975 (Offsite-box 3164, Folder 27)
    - Middle East: News Tour: News Summary, 1975 (Offsite-box 3164, Folder 28)
    - Middle East: Peace Proposal, 1975 (Offsite-box 3164, Folder 29)
    - Middle East: Trip: 1984 March 17-29, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 3164, Folder 30)
    - Middle East Trip: 1984 March 17-29 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R44)
    - Miller, Loye W., 1958-1970 (Offsite-box 3165, Folder 1)
    - Miller, Loye W. [RESTRICTED], 1958, 1970 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Miller, Loye W. Jr., 1969 (Offsite-box 3165, Folder 2)
    - Miller, Loye W, Jr. [RESTRICTED], 1966-1970 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Miller, Loye and Murray Gart Party: Chicago, undated (Offsite-box 3165, Folder 3-4)
    - Mindszenty, Joseph (Cardinal), 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 3165, Folder 5)
    - Missing Journalists [EMPTY], undated (Offsite-box 3165, Folder 6)
    - Mission X, 1986 (Offsite-box 3165, Folder 7)
    - Mitchell, William, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 3165, Folder 8)
    - Mohr, Charles, 1961-1963 (Offsite-box 3165, Folder 9)
    - Mohr, Charles [RESTRICTED], 1963 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Mondale, Walter: Coffee, 1958-1970 (Offsite-box 3165, Folder 10)
    - Mondale: Walter: Lunch, 1976 (Offsite-box 3165, Folder 11)
    - Money, 1974 (Offsite-box 3165, Folder 12)
    - Money, 1972, 1980 (Offsite-box 3165, Folder 13)
    - Montreal [EMPTY], undated (Offsite-box 3165, Folder 14)
    - Morin, Leish, 1973-1978 (Offsite-box 3165, Folder 15-16)
    - Morin, Leish [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Moritz, Michael, 1976-1984 (Offsite-box 3165, Folder 17)
    - Moritz, Michael [RESTRICTED], 1979-1984 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Morris, Fred: Torture Case, 1974 (Offsite-box 3165, Folder 18)
    - Morse, Robert, 1960-1965 (Offsite-box 3165, Folder 19)
    - Moscow, 1960, 1969-1982 (Offsite-box 3165, Folder 20-22)
    - Moscow [RESTRICTED], 1972-1973 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Moscow: Accreditation, 1970-1973, 1983 (Offsite-box 3165, Folder 23-25)
    - Moscow: Expulsion, 1964-1967 (Offsite-box 3165, Folder 26)
    - Moscow: Personnel, 1962-1969, 1981 (Offsite-box 3165, Folder 27)
    - Moscow: Visa Problems, 1962-1966, 1972 (Offsite-box 3165, Folder 28)
    - Moving Policy, undated (Offsite-box 3165, Folder 29)
    - Muller, Henry, 1975 (Offsite-box 3165, Folder 30)
    - Muller, Henry: Expenses, 1986 (Offsite-box 3165, Folder 31)
    - Muller, Henry: Travel, 1986 (Offsite-box 3165, Folder 32)
    - Muller, Henry: Vacations, 1986 (Offsite-box 3165, Folder 33)
    - Mulliken, John, 1959-1974 (Offsite-box 3165, Folder 34-35)
    - Mulliken, John [RESTRICTED], 1974-1976 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Murphy, Jamie, 1979 (Offsite-box 3166, Folder 1)
    - Muskie, Edmund, 1971 (Offsite-box 3166, Folder 2)
    - Mydans, Carl, 1944-1959, 1975 (Offsite-box 3166, Folder 3)
    - N: Miscellaneous [EMPTY], undated (Offsite-box 3166, Folder 4)
    - Nairobi, 1963-1978 (Offsite-box 3166, Folder 5-8)
    - Nairobi: Personnel, 1962-1969 (Offsite-box 3166, Folder 9)
    - Nairobi: Personnel [RESTRICTED], 19687,1978 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Nairobi: Stringers, 1963-1969 (Offsite-box 3166, Folder 10)
    - Nairobi: Stringers [RESTRICTED], 1964 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Nation: Covers, 1972-1974 (Offsite-box 3166, Folder 11)
    - Nation: List, 1975 (Offsite-box 3166, Folder 12)
    - National Foreign Trade Council, 1968 (Offsite-box 3166, Folder 13)
    - National Foreign Trade Council Meeting: Waldorf: 1965 November 17 (Offsite-box 3166, Folder 14)
    - National Press Foundation: Spanish Language Fellowship, 1986 (Offsite-box 3166, Folder 15)
    - Neale, Mike, 1970 (Offsite-box 3166, Folder 16)
    - Neale, Mike [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Neff, Donald, 1964-1978 (Offsite-box 3166, Folder 17-18)
    - Neff, Donald [RESTRICTED], 1965, 1978-1981 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Neff, Donald: Dispatches: 1974 Oct. 21 - Nov. 25 (Offsite-box 3166, Folder 19-24)
    - New Delhi, 1963-1980 (Offsite-box 3166, Folder 25-28)
    - New Delhi: Connaught Lodge, 1962-1965 (Offsite-box 3166, Folder 29)
    - New Delhi [RESTRICTED], 1965-1967 (Offsite-box R44)
    - New Delhi: Correspondence, 1969, 1975-1983 (Offsite-box 3166, Folder 30-31)
    - New Delhi: Life, 1958, 1965 (Offsite-box 3166, Folder 32)
    - New Delhi: Personnel, 1957-1967, 1975-1984 (Offsite-box 3166, Folder 33-34)
    - New Delhi: Stringers, 1962-1971 (Offsite-box 3166, Folder 35)
    - New Delhi: Time, 1958-1967 (Offsite-box 3167, Folder 1)
    - New Monday - Friday Schedule, 1974 (Offsite-box 3167, Folder 2)
    - New York, 1965-1984 (Offsite-box 3167, Folder 3)
    - New York City Incentive Comp., 1970 (Offsite-box 3167, Folder 4)
    - New York Times, undated (Offsite-box 3167, Folder 5)
    - New York World's Fair, 1963-1965 (Offsite-box 3167, Folder 6)
    - Newman, Pat, 1973-1977 (Offsite-box 3167, Folder 7)
    - Newman, Pat [RESTRICTED], 1971-1978 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Newman, Patricia, 1970-1976 (Offsite-box 3167, Folder 8)
    - Newman, Patricia [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Offsite-box R44)
    - News Bureau: Linen Presentation: 1961 Dec. (Offsite-box 3167, Folder 9)
    - News Bureau: Operations, 195233-1960 (Offsite-box 3167, Folder 10-14)
    - News Bureau: Operations [RESTRICTED], undated (Offsite-box R44)
    - News Bureau: Personnel, 1956-1960 (Offsite-box 3167, Folder 15)
    - News Bureau: Personnel [RESTRICTED], 1955-1959 (Offsite-box R44)
    - News Desk, 1969-1985 (Offsite-box 3167, Folder 16-19)
    - News Desk [RESTRICTED], 11978 (Offsite-box R44)
    - News Desk: Personnel, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3167, Folder 20)
    - News Desk: Personnel [RESTRICTED], 1976-1978 (Offsite-box R44)
    - News Service, 1973-1983 (Offsite-box 3167, Folder 21)
    - News Service: Budget, 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 3167, Folder 22)
    - News Service: Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1975 (Offsite-box 3167, Folder 23)
    - News Service: Correspondence: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Offsite-box R44)
    - News Service: Headcount, 1962-1965 (Offsite-box 3167, Folder 24)
    - News Service: History, 1969, 1978 (Offsite-box 3167, Folder 25)
    - News Service: Merger: 1972 April (Offsite-box 3167, Folder 26)
    - News Service: Miscellaneous, 1970, 1976 (Offsite-box 3167, Folder 27)
    - News Service: Raises [RESTRICTED], 1975-1978 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Newsday, 1966-1968 (Offsite-box 3167, Folder 28)
    - Newspaper Guild, 1973-1978 (Offsite-box 3167, Folder 29-31)
    - Newspaper Guild, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3168, Folder 1-6)
    - Newspaper Guild [RESTRICTED], 1972-1978 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Newspapers, 1968-1972 (Offsite-box 3168, Folder 7)
    - Newsstand Survey, 1970 (Offsite-box 3168, Folder 8)
    - Newstour, 1963-1978, undated (Offsite-box 3168, Folder 9-23)
    - Newstour: 1969, undated (Offsite-box 3264, Folder 7)
    - Newstour: 1969 [RESTRICTED], 1969, undated (Offsite-box R45)
    - Newstour: Asia, 1963-1965 (Offsite-box 3168, Folder 24)
    - Newstour: Asia, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 3169, Folder 1-4)
    - Newstour: Asia: 1965: Blue Book, 1965-1966 (Offsite-box 3169, Folder 5)
    - Newstour: Asia: Cables and Wires, 1965 (Offsite-box 3169, Folder 6-7)
    - Newstour: Asia: Greenbook, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 3169, Folder 8)
    - Newstour: Backgrounder Letters, 1963-1969 (Offsite-box 3169, Folder 9)
    - Newstour: Blue/Greenbook: 1969 Feb. (Offsite-box 3169, Folder 10)
    - Newstour: Bonus: 1985, 1986 (Offsite-box 3169, Folder 11)
    - Newstour: Daily News Summaries, 1975-1978 (Offsite-box 3169, Folder 12-13)
    - Newstour: Eastern Europe, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 3169, Folder 14)
    - Newstour: Eastern Europe: 1966 Oct.: Briefing (Offsite-box 3169, Folder 15)
    - Newstour: Eastern Europe: 1966 October: Participants [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R45)
    - Newstour: Europe: 1963 Nov. (Offsite-box 3169, Folder 16)
    - Newstour: Europe: Mailings to Businessmen, 1956, 1963-1964 (Offsite-box 3169, Folder 17-18)
    - Newstour: Europe: Proposed Businessmen's Trip, 1965 (Offsite-box 3169, Folder 19)
    - Newstour: Europe: Tour Reunion, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 3169, Folder 20)
    - Newstour: Far East: 1969 February [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R45)
    - Newstour: Japan: 1973 May (Offsite-box 3169, Folder 21-22)
    - Newstour: Middle East, 1975-1980, 1991 (Offsite-box 3169, Folder 23-24)
    - Newstour: Middle East, 1974-1978 (Offsite-box 3170, Folder 1-3)
    - Newstour: Proposed: 1969 Feb., 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 3170, Folder 4)
    - Newstour: Reports: American Businesses Abroad, 1966 (Offsite-box 3170, Folder 5)
    - Newstour: Reports: Attitudes toward Time, 1961 (Offsite-box 3170, Folder 6)
    - Newstour: Reports: Quality Files, 1965 (Offsite-box 3170, Folder 7-8)
    - Newstour: Reunion: 1963 Nov., 1964 (Offsite-box 3170, Folder 9)
    - Newstour: Rover Boys!!! on Grand Tour, 1963 (Offsite-box 3170, Folder 10-11)
    - Newstour: Soviet Union, 1963 (Offsite-box 3170, Folder 12-16)
    - Newstour: Tour for Businessmen, 1965 (Offsite-box 3170, Folder 17)
    - Newstour: United States: 1969 May: Background Material (Offsite-box 3170, Folder 18)
    - Newstour: United States: European Businessmen, 1969 (Offsite-box 3170, Folder 19)
    - Newstour: United States: European Businessmen: 1969 May 3-10: Cancelled (Offsite-box 3170, Folder 20)
    - Newstour: United States: Report on America for European Businessmen, 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 3170, Folder 21)
    - Newstour: United States: Report on America for European Businessmen, 1971 (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 1)
    - Newstour: Update on America: 1977 Oct.: European Businessmen (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 2)
    - Newsweek, 1977 (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 3)
    - Newton, Mary, 1969-1971 (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 4)
    - Newton, Mary [RESTRICTED], 1969-1970 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Nguyen, Dang [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Nicaragua, 1977 (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 5-7)
    - Nichols, Hollis Alexander, 1970-1973 (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 8)
    - Nichols, Hollis Alexander [RESTRICTED], 970-1973 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Nieman, Foundation: Dinner, 1970 (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 9)
    - Nitze, Paul: Lunch, 1978 (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 10)
    - Nixon, Richard, 1978 (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 11-12)
    - Nixon, Richard: Fund, 1960 (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 13)
    - Nixon, Richard: Resignation Letter, 1974 (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 14)
    - Noble, Sara [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Nordio, Umberto, 1977 (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 15)
    - North Viet Nam, 1963-1967 (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 16-17)
    - Northeastern University, 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 18)
    - O: Miscellaneous [EMPTY], undated (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 19)
    - Office Space, 1971 (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 20)
    - Office Space, undated (Offsite-box 3264, Folder 8)
    - Ogle, Ed, 1958-1986 (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 21-23)
    - Ogle, Ed [RESTRICTED], 1965, 1974-1979 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Olympics: Moscow: 1980, 1978-1980 (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 24-25)
    - Olympics: Winter: Sapporo, 1971 (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 26)
    - Ottawa, 1962-1985 (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 27-29)
    - Ottawa [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Ottawa: Move, 1971 (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 30)
    - Ottawa: Move [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Out of Town Correspondents: Convention, 1976 (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 31)
    - Outstanding Men, 19764-1965 (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 32-33)
    - Overseas Bureau Personnel, 1946, 1960-1964 (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 34)
    - Overseas Press Club: Dinner, 1974, undated (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 35-36)
    - P: Miscellaneous, 1967-1971 (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 37)
    - Pace, Frank, 1976 (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 38)
    - Paike, Too Chin: Lunch, 1979 (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 39)
    - Palestinians, 1975 (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 40)
    - Paris, 1965-1985 (Offsite-box 3171, Folder 41-44)
    - Paris, 1972-1974 (Offsite-box 3172, Folder 1)
    - Paris, 1976 (Offsite-box 3264, Folder 9)
    - Paris: Fortune, 1964 (Offsite-box 3172, Folder 2)
    - Paris: Life, 1960-1964 (Offsite-box 3172, Folder 3)
    - Paris: Personnel, 1964-1972 (Offsite-box 3172, Folder 4-5)
    - Paris: Personnel [RESTRICTED], 1966 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Paris: Photographic Stringers, 1959-1961, 1973 (Offsite-box 3172, Folder 6)
    - Paris: Sports Illustrated, 1957-1967 (Offsite-box 3172, Folder 7)
    - Paris: Stringers, 1963-1967, 1973 (Offsite-box 3172, Folder 8)
    - Paris: Time, 1972-1974 (Offsite-box 3172, Folder 9)
    - Paris: Time [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Paris Match, 1958-1961 (Offsite-box 3172, Folder 10)
    - Passports, Visas, and Work Permits: Foreign Nationals, 1969 (Offsite-box 3172, Folder 11)
    - Paul, Tony, 1977 (Offsite-box 3172, Folder 12)
    - Payoff: Aburish, Abu Said: Son's Book Proposal, 1984 (Offsite-box 3172, Folder 13)
    - Pending, 1973-1975 (Offsite-box 3172, Folder 14)
    - Pension Plan, 1956-1965 (Offsite-box 3172, Folder 15-16)
    - Pension Plan: Bonn Bureau, 1957-1965 (Offsite-box 3172, Folder 17-18)
    - People, 1973-1979 (Offsite-box 3172, Folder 19-20)
    - People: Budget, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 3172, Folder 21)
    - People: Stringers, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 3172, Folder 22)
    - Personnel, 1973-1978 (Offsite-box 3172, Folder 23-24)
    - Personnel [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Offsite-box R45)
    - Peru, 1962 (Offsite-box 3172, Folder 25-26)
    - Philippines: Marco's Libel Case, 1971 (Offsite-box 3172, Folder 27)
    - Picture Department, 1974 (Offsite-box 3172, Folder 28)
    - Picture Payments, 1956-1965, 1971 (Offsite-box 3172, Folder 29)
    - Pioneer Press, 1969-1972 (Offsite-box 3172, Folder 30)
    - Policy, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3173, Folder 31)
    - Political Conference: 1976, 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 3172, Folder 32)
    - Political Correspondents Whereabouts, 1976 (Offsite-box 3172, Folder 33)
    - Political Meeting: 1980 Jan. 12-14, 1978-1980 (Offsite-box 3173, Folder 1-3)
    - Political Swing: #1: South: 1976 Sept. (Offsite-box 3173, Folder 4)
    - Political Swing: #2: West: 1976 October (Offsite-box 3173, Folder 5)
    - Political Swing: #3: Midwest: 1976 Oct. (Offsite-box 3173, Folder 6)
    - Polk, William, 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 3173, Folder 7)
    - Polls and Surveys, 1972, undated (Offsite-box 3173, Folder 8-9)
    - Portable Terminals, 1977 (Offsite-box 3173, Folder 10)
    - Portugal, 1959-1961 (Offsite-box 3173, Folder 11)